Guide to the George P. Garrett Papers, 1929-2008 (bulk 1960-2000)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2008-0181)
  The addition (760 items; 1.2 lin. ft.; dated 1999-2008) contains notes, research, and drafts of Garrett’s short story The Source, eventually renamed Thanksgiving. There are also some folders of correspondence, transcripts of interviews, and some audiovisual material including four audiocassette tapes and one DVD.
  - Source: Roger Casement (Box 1)
  - Source: Angel Falls (Box 1)
  - Source: Long Steel Knives (Box 1)
  - Source: Photos, Dickey expedition (Box 1)
  - Source: Thanksgiving (Box 1)
  - Source notes, April 3, 2007 (Box 1)
  - Source: Events (Box 1)
  - Source: Miscellaneous clippings (Box 1)
  - Source: Early draft (Box 1)
  - Source: Orinoco (Box 1)
  - Ciudad Bolivar (Box 1)
  - Source: News and headlines, 1931 (Box 1)
  - Source: Miscellaneous notes (Box 1)
  - Ralegh Creature on Map (Box 1)
  - Venezuela flags (Box 1)
  - Source: Draft of Intro (Box 1)
  - Source: Epigraph (Box 1)
  - Source: Misc. notes on the Orinoco (Box 1)
  - Source: Draft, pages 1-21 (Box 1)
  - Source: Early draft (Box 1)
  - National Geographic (Nov. 1933) (Box 1)
  - National Geographic (Nov. 1931) (Box 1)
  - Source: Possible ending draft (Box 1)
  - Source: Etc (notebook) (Box 1)
  - Source: Draft of ending (Box 1)
  - Garrett interviews (1-2) (Box 1)
  - Garrett interviews (3) (Box 2)
  - George Garrett poems (Box 2)
  - Correspondence (Box 2)
  - Source: Miscellaneous (unfoldered material) (Box 2)
  - George Garrett's birth certificate (Box 2)
  - 4 Audiocassettes
    - New Letters on the Air (Box 2)
    - John Ciardi: Speaking of Words (Box 2)
    - American Audio Prose Library readings (Box 2)
    - The King of Babylon Shall Not Come Against You partial reading (Box 2)
  - Key to the City of Knoxville (Box 2)
- Accession (2008-0271)
  The addition (375 items; 0.6 lin. ft.; dated 1985-2008) contains correspondence; drafts and notes for poems and other projects, including an Armies of Occupation project; and copies of newspaper clippings and interviews with Garrett.
  - Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Clippings and interviews, (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Armies of Occupation: Thomas Dixon Jr. (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Notes for Armies of Occupation (notebook) (Box 1)
  - My summer reading etc. DLB (Box 1)
  - Armies of Occupation: Leftovers etc (Box 1)
  - Armies of Occupation: DLB (Box 1)
  - Armies of Occupation: Miscellaneous (Box 1)
  - Armies of Occupation: Ongoing (Box 1)
  - Armies of Occupation: Notes (Box 1)
  - Armies of Occupation: Notes and Source (notebook) (Box 1)
  - Armies of Occupation: Marines (Box 1)
  - Evangelista (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous materials (unfoldered) (Box 1)
  - Hollins Conference notes (Box 1)
- Accession (2013-0168)
  Addition (Acc. 2013-0168) (50 items, 0.1 lin. ft.; dated 1964-1972) comprises a file of letters to Garrett from those whose last names begin with the letter "P."
  - Correspondence (Box 1)
  - to Garrett, Last name begins "P", (1 folder) (Box 1)